<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Rails Network FAQ</title>
    <link>https://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Rails Network FAQ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://yourdomain.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adding Rails Network to MetaMask</title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/docs/rails-network/add-rails-to-metamask/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/docs/rails-network/add-rails-to-metamask/</guid>
      <description>Adding Rails Network to MetaMask # On smartphones:&#xA;Open MetaMask and tap on the network list at the top of the app. Press Add Network. Select Custom Network tab. In this dialog, use the following variables: Network Name: Rails Network RPC URL: https://mainnet.steamexchange.io Currency Symbol: STEAMX Chain ID: 6278 Explorer: https://explore.steamexchange.io Then click on Add to have our network in your Network list. On extension:&#xA;Open MetaMask extension and tap on the network list at the top-left of the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from BSC to Rails</title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/docs/general/how-to-migrate-from-bsc-to-rails/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/docs/general/how-to-migrate-from-bsc-to-rails/</guid>
      <description>How to Migrate SteamX Tokens from BSC to Rails Network # Migrating your tokens from BSC to Rails network is a straightforward process. You can watch a video tutorial on how to do it or follow these easy steps:&#xA;Use a Compatible Wallet: Ensure you are using a compatible wallet. We strongly recommend MetaMask. If you already have SteamX (BSC) tokens in another wallet, you can import your Seed Phrase into MetaMask and continue using the other wallet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With ToC</title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/docs/trading/with-toc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/docs/trading/with-toc/</guid>
      <description>Caput vino delphine in tamen vias # Cognita laeva illo fracta # Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.&#xA;Te at cruciabere vides rubentis manebo Maturuit in praetemptat ruborem ignara postquam habitasse Subitarum supplevit quoque fontesque venabula spretis modo Montis tot est mali quasque gravis Quinquennem domus arsit ipse Pellem turis pugnabant locavit Natus quaerere # Pectora et sine mulcere, coniuge dum tincta incurvae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is SteamX</title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Steam Exchange, a pioneering Canadian Fintech startup established in 2021, stands at the forefront of the rapidly evolving landscape of cryptocurrency, blockchain technology, and web2 to web3 integrations. Our core values revolve around fostering a culture of continuous learning, driving innovation, and offering scalable digital asset solutions. As a registered corporation in Canada, we are committed to reshaping the way value is exchanged by leveraging cutting-edge technologies and a unique hybrid model that harmonizes elements from both centralized and decentralized financial ecosystems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/docs/hidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/docs/hidden/</guid>
      <description> This page is hidden in menu # </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
